Sorry guys can you hear me? Yeah, it's just a little bit a little bit crazy
There's a lot of good people and I think that you know
There are people with like different
Temperaments different
This is just for all different people and it's amazing people get along so well they do even though they don't always get along
Do you want people to get along? Okay, can we now get good?
Okay, my link and what's up guys. Hi everybody
Yeah, hi JT
Yeah, it's getting a little bit
I mean some of it was funny with like mr.. Mr.. Big Pies when you get hardly here when he was like yelling at himself in the back
but that was kind of funny and
You know, even though Crystal is like accusing me of things I would never say and I never said I
Thought it was kind of funny that she was accusing me
It was just like it's so off the wall, but people might believe that it's like that's kind of scary
That's the
You're saying I called you things are in my vocabulary that I would never call anybody. Okay, it's not even if it isn't
My worst insults are not anything close to those
Oh nightmare give me 15 dislikes. Oh, that's not very nice
But no
How many students I lost I lost count about a million, you know, but
I'm like flooded in life
Hi, Lulu
How
Exclave I'm really like a maybe I do have I am a descendant from the cheddar bands
There's like one of the oldest bodies in England is found and it has like dark skin and blue eyes
Or he does and you know, he's one of the oldest
found
corpses or mummy, I don't know if he's a more of a mummy and
I'm related to him
Hi everybody, thanks for coming back. It's the 320 a.m. in Los Angeles
Hmm, I was drinking one beer I might drink another couple
All this the bagel shop over to six I guess maybe I'll get a bagel today. I
Love you guys. Hey, you're there tricks. Yeah, I'm sitting over here on the couch next to me. Come on, babe. Come over here
Yeah, but it's like, you know, it really is I mean, it's really difficult like his I love a lot a lot. I love
I love my audience. I love the people I meet the people come on the panel
I really love I really like my heart. I think about a dream about them
I have a heart. I love them. I love the Alex even though and even though everyone hated him
I was still like, you know, I don't care. I don't care everyone hates me because they also I'll still be his friend
Then he just turned on me tonight and just
said something like this really hurtful things and
Kind of went off on me and I didn't I didn't provoke it. Have I drank water recently? I probably need to go
I'm drying up. I'm drinking some beer
Go sit outside double trouble. You miss Alex. Yeah, well, they yeah, I mean, uh, well, he's only gone for a few hours
But you know, yeah, the streams are gone. You know, it's one clips them clip an hour for over hold your peace
I just
People are trying to ruin them.
What can you do?
I'm considering like, you know, really cutting,
I'm considering just doing shorter shows
and then really cutting down the panel time
and then in that shorter panel time
just really be really selective of who I let on.
I just,
I've been streaming so much that he wins the times to stream and also when I just feel like it, which I always do
No, you know, you know, I love doing this
But it becomes becomes more more
More
Wories worries and problems and fun
I don't know how much longer I'll do it but
Because I'm really about doing what I love. I love this and it's like it's the same that people
wanna
I'm not a mean person. I'm not a addicted person. I'm not
People someone did hurt me. I wouldn't even see vengeance or anything. I would just like forgive them because I'm just for getting person
And I really am
You'll think if you look at me fake and I all I think I'm gonna call everything I got like I'm gonna call everything here
Yeah, every I used to really to be a streamer, especially I don't know I wasn't as
Strong in myself and like loving myself as much as I didn't trust myself. I wouldn't I don't think I would I would last
I think my mind would have
I'm a weak channel owner. Okay, JT well JT, you know
You are a week
You're a week
Panel guest and chatter and so kick rocks
Yeah, he did I mean I've now I've now he's banned them, you know, and there's no way from to talk on the show
Or maybe you can go an alternate accounts or something but
Yeah, well, like I said guys, it's like I don't care you can like think anything you want, but
You're not gonna just insult me on my own channel, you know, and I'm so weak
Yeah, bye JT
Am I so weak?
You know, I you know
My life, you know exactly what I've been through and why I'm why I'm here and
You know any of that? No, you know how you know
If I was a week, why am I still on this earth?
Thank you. If I'm so weak, how did I make it this far? How do I last for the average life expectancy of a gay man is like
33 years old or something like that. I'm already 44. So I'm already past my life expectancy. All my life now is just a bonus, okay?
Hi, good morning, Hannah. Thank you for being here
We'll see a man. I got the link pinned
I just don't like I don't like to be called weak because I'm not weak. I'm like
I have strength, but you know if you look at the strength tarot card, you know, you know who represents strength
Some some people will sometimes say oh women are weak and you know men are strong
I don't believe that I think women are strong and men can be weak and also with the strength the strength tarot card is a woman
Okay, with the lion. Okay, and so it's not it's a metaphor for
Using gentleness and like love and like you know instead of like a force force and like
You know all these other tactics you like
It's gentleness of strength, you know
Yeah, I trust the mods and now that I've seen a model of people that were not being good mods or just
Yeah
I was I was I was sitting right there. I was sitting in this. I was I was seeing it. I was just
Just watching don't let anyone ruin your vibe people talk, but let them
It shows their weakness. Yeah, I agree. That's why that's why I do let people talk
And I was and they had stepped up. I stepped off a lot the past few days is to this watch and
Let people talk and reveal themselves right like lights. Thank you. It's a different vibe. Yeah, it's a really cool light
It's actually really cool my wall so you can see makes a rubber borealis on the wall, but I just had that lit up in front of me
Hi
Looks like my kind of a blue mist
Yeah, it's really cool. I got it on a on T move for like six bucks shipped
Yep, thank you. Good morning, Ilya
Yeah, I mean, I mean I don't problem with him, but then he's just like insulting my shit
I just had enough of personal insults tonight, and you know
I'll probably do mass unbanned and you know if it's some it's that big of a deal
I don't I don't even know why some people come to the channel other than just to cause problems like I
Mean he's cordial and he's nice, but
Sometimes that can be a tactic just to get on you know the good side of the host and so you can get away with everything
so
I always because then Goddy was like saying the same thing. He's like, oh, you're weaker. You have no backbone. You have no spine
That was it on the panel some I was just watching trying to
Reserve what's the weather looking like today in the beaches a good channel will quickly go down on the wrong people keep it
happening good
Yeah
Yeah, I gotta I gotta I'm just trying to get the right people here. It's like it's hard because
You know, there's people that don't like gay people. I don't know if it's has any you're gonna do with that really
I heard their other agenda. It just seems like they're just doing weird shit
And then there's the minute they're and also they're just like and then they're being really cocky about it
Like I don't like that's a thing. It's like it's called like your smug
It's like smug or I think smug is the word or it's like
Hmm. Oh, we own this channel. Look at we wear up. We do be like it's like, okay. No, it's like
Graciously welcomes you here was friendly to you let you on the panel for hours joke joke
I just I was nothing but cordial and then they're they're gonna like
Turn on me like that. No, I just have to know
Like I said these outside of groups. I have no idea about I
Have just show up places and you know
Ericka, yeah, but Ericka, but then the smug is like a little like a little too bruised to light. So now, oh, we we're like we're
We were like, they're fooling somebody or something. You know, yeah, Ericka. Yeah
Yeah, hello, hey girl
Like the guy, the guy that tonight, you know, they're saying, you know, it was a very nice couple that came on and he just seemed like he was like, well, I was told that he was using my picture on your show.
He said, I saw you told him not to do that. And he's like, thank you. It was just a cordial thing, rather than, oh, can you please not put a picture, JT, and then JT keeps putting up pictures, right?
Whatever I mean
Who can who's to judge how fast or slow people are you know, there's
everyone has some kind of
Divine intelligence beyond like just the brain. There's there's some kind of like, you know, there's there's a heart. There's the heart intelligence. There's the
Kindness intelligence. There's the wanting to learn there's wanting to improve. What's up, Nick? How are you just hanging in there?
Hang out in the midst
I think it's a purple.
Yeah, well, yeah.
Yeah, nice little change.
Wow, it looks like guys,
it looks like there's like a dark something
in the, I don't know if I can show you,
but it looks like there's a dark shadow on the,
I don't know where it's coming from.
That's really weird.
It's really kind of scary.
It looks like there's some kind of floating ghost
or something.
I feel like we're moving from that I swear his exact word easily manipulated well you know
I like I have a saying I'm not as dumb as I look okay or I was born in the morning
But not yesterday morning something like that
Cool
And it's like, well, wow, is that a thing to brag about?
If you're an expert manipulator,
finding the easiest to manipulate people
and messing with them, is that anything to brag about?
It's kind of called a bully
or picking on the weaker, right?
I don't know.
Yeah, people that are just like people at breakfast. It's like somebody stealing like the like so it's like some
It's like the pen is a blind man. He's a wallet
So he depends on the people that give them the correct change
It's like someone like taking in the hundred dollar bill out of the wall keeping the dollar back, right?
And then say, huh? Well, he's just do you blind? He didn't see and I want money. So
Right
Yeah, he was being terrible and I mean I saw and I was
Just observing just observing right sometimes it's smart to observe
Like I said people always reveal themselves the mask will never sound for very long
And that's why it's also why I'll have controversial people on here
Because they can like reveal themselves savage owl. Hey girl sassy Jeff
How's everybody yeah, I'm another couple beers actually what is that? It's uh,
Amazon or Amazon Arizona iced tea part the hard one
Ellen Jalen, okay
They blew a while longer hopefully we have a nice weekend guys
Talk to quite a start. Hey Jeff. How are you?
Yeah
Things are good a good yeah, I'm just I'm slowly gonna try to you know, I kind of like
Let some of the inmates run the asylum so to speak for a little while you know
Yeah, sometimes
Now I'm still learning. I learned that's not a very good idea to do. I want the inmates running asylum
I need to be the nurse ratchet here, right?
Yeah, there we go. There's next new video premiering make sure to check out his new premiere
Hello shorty
Yeah, but it's it's like it's like when people
That are my supposed to my friends that I care about and I've always been kind of I don't insult and I don't not mean to
when they just come at me out of nowhere over nothing nothing I did and it's like I
Still know
Like
Makes me feel bad for people that are just like you know
the victims of that. I'm sure there's been a lot of people there just victims of bullies or
right. You look at me through my nurse ratchet. Maybe for Halloween I'll do a nurse ratchet.
I'm just trying to talk to you. Oh yeah, so I think he's in here. It might be on the panel soon.
So how's this look? Oh, there we go. I'll do green also in the like the murky
poison swaps
If we're cleaning out this green like the green it's like, you know, it's like the heart shockers
We're seeing this heart heart essence
But it's like it's a good release of all this negativity all the poison
That eventually will turn to purple
Thank you promise. It's not you you're correct
They're like, yeah, I mean, I yeah, you're right. I've seen on Benny's I saw on at least is the kind I would like that but
Emma is kind of more like really strict and stuff
He's a million band words and has a lot of timing of all these people were a little hardly anything but
Um, yeah, I, I, and I was in Benny's, I, they were calling all the mods there that said all the mods were those I'll call Benny that I see, I see it everywhere here and then on my chat and all the IP two chats, I see people being called that.
That's why I'm very hesitant to like, you know, leave every story here about people because everyone just says everything about people.
I'm sure a lot of people believe it, and it's probably very hurtful.
So I look like the Green Goblin tonight. It's not easy being, I look like a very Green Goblin, it's hot, so I have to,
oh wait a minute, are we, where are the, I don't know, I guess, I guess they, uh,
I don't know, I didn't see him pull up. Well, a JT's ban, but um
Yeah, I mean that that was one of the first like you know beat it, you know
That was because people were slandering people in her chat and she's like yeah
That was like one of the words don't say that word
But I don't like other words things said either
They see yeah, well JT's ban. I don't know where God is. I don't know where Rain is so
I just want I did some of the stuff they were saying tonight. It was like, okay
Not it was not very nice to me
Yeah, I mean, you know, they're probably you're already on other alls, that's okay. I mean, it's that can be in the chat. It's just like
Not type in the chat
I don't know. I don't know. Just behave in the chat. You know, I would have said you'd be in the chat, but you can't start insulting me. It's not very, not very, very nice.
Yeah, let's do the green light. Let's do the green fortune. There you go.
Growth, fortune, happiness. And we did a really good reading, too. Right?
Yeah, he just basically he said he said he said it's like you're weak you're weak channel owner
And that you know, it's not like the biggest thing, you know the biggest version you can say to somebody but it's like
You know, I feel like I've been
As far as I can be why I remember myself, I don't know I think it's just late
I do 37 people in the chat. I had a link hand if he wants to come up
I'm cleaning out the closet. I'm I'm cleaning out this room because then Alex was like it's like so funny because I clean
I've been cleaning out a lot and I have this whole room organized and vacuuming and stuff and then ask like oh you're disgusting
You're guilty or guilty person
And then you just saying like mean is like
It's coming out of nowhere, and then Arthur was kind of saying the same stuff, and that's kind of like the memes
We're like, oh, then Mr. Big Pops is like I smell like fish talk or it's not like talk tacos and I need to take a shit
it's like
If I ever if I if you meet me in person, I think it's like that's one thing but it's like you're gonna judge me through the
My show and it's like, you know, I I don't really like not like a big sweater or anything or
I don't care if people are kind or what, the kind,
they fuck everybody, keep the fuck, yeah.
I know, it was just like, what are they doing?
It's like, it just makes everybody else uncomfortable
in that chat, and it's like, and it's kind of like,
and people, if there's new people,
they'll be like, what's going on?
What kind of chat is this?
It's just like, but it's like this.
I guess it's IP2 kind of vibe people have it's like they're just obsessed
It's like there's obsessed with it because it's like they figure out
Oh, there's like here's the here's the thing that like I will get you know this person
You know depressed and you know what on the on the verge of you know
Despair right they eventually to their true cause I'm glad if I saw yeah, I mean I had an idea
I was trying to like
You know say I say that I didn't believe it
And Alex was his theories were not all right, but
And there's something go right and so but I was trying not to like
not to
Give it away, but now it's out
they're playing the game of of
Tease
They're playing the game of cheese I
Need to join post link link is in the link pants. I didn't get home. Sorry
I can do it, it's a pen.
Posted it again.
Yeah, it's just...
I mean, yeah, it's fun sometimes when, you know, I have wild chats and wild panels and people are saying outrageous things.
Stale it's kind of that kind of it's like to me. It's like that's not
That's not fine. It's like there's a lot of people will go in there's a lot of people. They're not
Being supportive of me like there's nothing anything nice. They're I'm talking to me or acknowledge you me at all
it's like
At least at least like it's like if you come to my my chat at least say hi to me, you know
the dead link
I don't have the ties. I don't know
Dead link, I'll post again. I don't know what's going on. I might have to restart again because it's the links not working. Hold on
Try that one
Shit, I don't know why it's not posting every post
Shit
They're working
Yeah, I know and then it's like and then I'd be like, you know, then he bit you
Guy would be really weird. I thought he was cool. I was like, I thought he was like the most relatable or like the most, you know
No, okay. I feel like I could talk to him out of everybody and like he was who's cool actually and
then
But he would just do weird shit like he
He was like
Things just like we start whispering under his voice like kind of like evil things like I just like we're everyone's gonna die
At least it's like we're kind of like dark things and like I was like can you just stop I just call it doom doom muttering or something
Yes, look up say mr. Big Pies person this place
Poison, mac, or baby, I have no idea, I have no idea.
It's like some other kind of, I don't know if there's somebody in my chat they didn't
like and then they started.
begging for rents, and then they're like,
oh, then they sort of tie people out
and they change their profile photos to like put people
up there, they post links of weird things
of like disabled minors and stuff
and the thumbnail of other people that,
other people, so it's just weird,
like it's just weird stuff.
And I was like, can you please stop doing that?
And then they would keep doing it.
Yeah.
Just seeing Kessner, like a prayer.
Obviously, I don't see you. I don't see you. I don't see you in the backstage.
So I need to restart the stream and, like, do another...
It's Link Dead.
If the link is dead, I'll just talk for like a few moments and I'll I'll try to sort the panel if I can but I need to mass on
Band you have some real month. I don't think I I did I did mass on band the other night Charlie and so I think everyone
band is on my doing
You think jelly dorks get triggered because they dedicate their lives to pay for mod
energy weirdo stuff
Did I just come in and chill?
The dead link, okay. No, I apologize. I
Can't really do anything about it. I just accept and the stream is sort of another one
So I'll do this. I'll just do it in a few minutes
Yeah
Or maybe oh, I don't know. Maybe I'll just I'll call I can call it a night. It's been a little bit wild on the panel
then I don't know if
Anyone anyone has oh shit, I mean hi
Can't sure I'm sorry. Yeah, well, I'll have it all the chat tomorrow
All the chat tomorrow, it's just like you know
It's been a little bit hectic today. I don't know maybe I'll do another panel, but I'm having a more beer. Maybe
I don't know if the link I just checked is done.
Like I'm on the moon or something
Yeah, I just think I'll just do like a little no chat. Sorry. Um, I know I love you ghost
Let me steer the ship a little bit
So
Why the fuck it's so hard to play
Oh
I think Mr. Big Pops just learned it. He sounds like he was learning it out of my show. So I'll grab a beer
Let's grab. I'll just have the RISD
Recall it
Yeah, oh, yeah, everyone's cooking
There's I don't know I cuz I'm not really I'm not really like you know cooking channel. I'm like more of a
That one together sure let's help me together. I'll grab it
Okay, cheers guys
a little bit scary and put a purple like that.
Yeah.
For the cats, well, there's one right here.
There's one right there.
We got up from a little cow or so.
I don't know if you went outside or something.
You, yeah.
Let's get out of here.
It's starting to kind of drink, you know, you know,
break up when we're drinking.
Hey babe, fun.
Hi babe.
I've noticed that like sometimes when we have friendships
and then we'll get in a fight with somebody.
to pay attention to the things they say when they're angry.
I'm not saying all the time. It's like what they're thinking, but I'm thinking
like just like you know what Alex was saying tonight when he I think he might have been mad at me
but just the stuff he was saying that's what he I guess he always thought that but he was always
he would never say anything like that to me before he never said even we fought before he
never said anything like that and then he was just went off for no reason when we were like I'm
Confusion, right?
So I do apologize the link's not working I guess for the for the
For the streamer panel, but I might start a new panel at 4 a.m. If you guys feel like it, but I
Appreciate mr. Big Pies performing but
It's a big pipes. I think it will set because you are a good musician
So it sounds so much better with an appropriate microphone because it's just
You were actually like on the five. It's not like you were like a five percent volume. I
Know I know BB, but I think people are saying it's not working some occasionally the link will not work
I don't know why it doesn't work
Show the names of the book I've crossed that way.
I still have to cross that GT name, but hold on, let's see.
Show you the book here.
Okay.
Well, I mean, it's not that many.
I haven't crossed out that many yet, but.
Okay.
Okay, so GTC.
JT on my books
See in the books see
Have like
There's a group I can't you can't it's hard to see I'm sorry. Yeah, it's a big Rob GT
I want to do it. Don't you see this is Rob Q the first page to Alice's cross out
And then
Well, I guess it's AC wasn't in here last night.
Huh.
Yeah.
It's a listen. No, it's it's my it's my be kind list. It's like it's like for my show
It's just it's just a way to like keep track of like who comes in the chat and you know their role and
If they do good things like it's a little gold star a little star, but we do bad things for the little
Little it's like it's the older kind of pants because it's not coming up. It's okay. Hold on
It is hold on try that
Try this link. I posted the same one that's posted with the pen.
Well, I haven't really like started the stars that much
I mean I put down with their mods and members and their name and stuff and then I can just cross out stuff as they go
I can just do like
It'll be chronological so I'll simply be able to tell who's like newer and stuff and
Detail lecture. I'll give you like a big I'll give her a few stars. There's three stars
Lot of people deserve stars
stars
So do you want to start the star Joe the excess garlic that's this color
Star keeping your teachers I'm I'm muted you mr. Big Pipe. Oh my god
What it means to be crossed the book is like basically
Yeah, you're not you're
Banned it's really a band if they're crossed out
Or if I might do another list of the if they start going off after that, but
You know, you know how you know how forgiving I am and
I just I hate that idea of like I hate the idea of like, you know, if I was mad at somebody and then it's like, yeah
Thank you. Don't let a viewer any
Tiny pipe in the street people just keep us your viewers. Oh
Yeah, you want to be in the book, but you don't want to be crossed out of the book, right?
And it's not the old link is the like the one in this chat. I don't know if I can look on my phone
There's another way
Your link I might have to start a new stream
I'll do it at four.
I'm muted on your sixth jam.
But Mr. Bigpipes, truthfully, we could barely hear,
like the music was, first of all,
somehow your volume was like at 3%,
like at 3% of loudness.
And I didn't do that.
And I tried to turn it up, it was still,
it was down, you can hear it.
Second of all,
It's like kind of like was going in and out like there's there's some kind of like
You get the link from in but yeah, that's the link I'm posting though
I like I keep out I keep hitting this one in this chat. I'm gonna try to refresh this chat. I'll try to get home
Try that guys
Restart I just refreshed my browser
What's wrong with you today
For all of me. Did you have a bad meal or something? What do you have a bad taco?
No, you have a bad talk. Why are you laughing on moody? Oh
My gosh, I just because I feel like I've been
You know through an emotional roller coaster and you know, I feel like I feel like people are kind of being
Mug or like, you know, I can't why are you allowing it? Why are you fucking allowing it into your head?
Just well, I'm I have I have to read the chat pay attention to it right because if I don't so then if you see you know
Naturally, you'll see your name and people are people who could consider friends are like calling you bad names or
saying total things and it's like I'm saying you but I'm saying you know Alex did it and and
You know it's happened like a few times and it's
It's hurtful, and it's like it's trying to kind of do you really in the show and then
Why are you laughing about it? You just called me a weird pedophile like ten minutes ago. I did not
I got it. I got it. No, I did not say that first of all
I do would never I would never call that I people were talking about you didn't do it. All right
You didn't do it. All right. You just agreed with somebody who wrote it
No, I don't see that might have been a misunderstanding the way I don't take it personally. That's what I I didn't say
Yes, you are
Don't don't let it affect your energy is what I'm saying site. I understand
I'm trying not to but it and I'm trying to be calm and you know
Reboot the energy. It's just there's a lot of like just people piling on and there's a lot of just I feel like this respect to
To me in the channel. It's not even like it's just like I so frustrating when I keep asking
Oh, please don't say this word.
It's like, not really that complicated.
I'm not saying you or, you know, but I'm saying,
I keep saying, don't say, and then people were saying it,
and it's like, I don't know if they're insane
or they're just malicious, or just a mixture of both,
because most people would should be able to,
they don't have to act in a restaurant,
you get a restaurant and you're gonna take a shit on the table.
They don't have to do that,
but they don't know how to act.
What's up?
What's so heavy?
Big thanks. Are you gonna come join the party shoot mr. Big reset reset your mindset and you'll be fine
Hold on I'll be right back
Can you hear me oh
Okay, I didn't know I didn't know if you could hear me or not
Yeah, we're here. Okay. Yeah, well you can see that it works. Yeah, that's good. Okay
How are you? Yeah, I got it cute. I'm getting ready to spot the space station and then I'm going to bed
Like it does flyovers and to put in your location and it'll and it'll let you know when it's gonna fly over like where you live
And so it's gonna fly over where I live like in one minute or so
Yeah
Yeah, I see here somebody's walking in the background. I hear a voice. I don't hear anything
Okay, I'm right here by myself. I'm outside. So I you might hear my
My bracelet hitting my watch
Maybe uh-huh. Oh, no, no, it's like it's I think mr. Big Pipes talking and
Is he up there? He's up there
Yeah, mr. Big Pipes is down. He's down. He's under there's Tiffany
Hello, can you hear me? Hi, how are you? Yeah. Hi, it's nice to get to talk to you. Yeah, you too. They're a friendly voice. Hi, VB. I don't hear anything.
I can't. I can't. Can you turn your mic up a little bit? Let me see. Yeah, for four minutes. Yeah, it's going to be dry flying over my house in like three minutes. So I'll be back. I just want to make sure to help you get it to work. But Goddy already came up. So.
Audio.
Nightmare, I can't make it. We're happy.
Can we get a wrap tonight, Mary?
I lose legs.
Thank you.
Yeah, that's what I wanted to tell you say I wanted to tell you that you got to remember at the end of the day
and this is your stream and
My suggestion to you as a stream owner myself
I don't have mods because I don't have a big stream like you do
But I would get with the good people that are gonna follow your roles and have good mods because
Because your stream is so popular and the the chat moves so fast
It's almost impossible for you to be able to read everything
He's like, I feel like Psyche, honestly, you deal with the shitheads and stalkers, I don't know, I get some really fucking nasty people, like the nastiest death threats and collars and shit, and it's like Psyche is in their fucking hand, in my opinion, he's controlled by those people.
though you can never let these people control you and you have all the power because he is like
i don't know like it seems like he recognized i don't know it's weird it's fucking weird
okay that's an interesting theory mr big pipes but you know as usual you're
wait why would you stand i've always been very nice to you psyche
Oh, yeah, okay. Well, no, no, I'm saying it was you're you're saying I'm I'm a part of like my the people trying to like hurt me
Like I don't you let you let people on here who call me a pedophile. I'm threatened. Okay. Okay. Okay. Bye
Bye. Yeah, cuz I don't like those words being said I might and stuff like that and
What you're bleeding me for other people you said to sit on your stream too. It's part of things
I get called those things everyone in the chat basically it's called those things are ever I have groves to fuck up
There's let's be a 40 year old man by mr. Big Place. I'd rather just have a nice put the conversation out here
Some guy bitch at me geez
I keep trying to tell you that in chat, you know, the one you need to please is yourself at the end of the day that you're doing this for fun, right?
So when it becomes not fun, if you come to the job, it becomes stressful.
That's what I said.
Trouble that it is fun and just enjoyment then it's like that's when it's probably time to wrap it up
I'm still I'm still I'm still a high level. I'm still like, you know, probably over 90% of you know, I like it back
And there's like it's like 10% it's like such shit and it's like I recognize it's like
It's just mostly bullshit, but you know, it does take its whole and it does like there are these emotional
Connections you make I make people that it's like because they're friends
And that's the hardest because then it's like when your friends start saying it should see you then people say well
There are they friends that person must you must really be bad because his friend his own friends are probably a piece of shit
So right that's what yeah, so listen
I've been here for a while and not your channel, but in this environment and I get it
I've had issues with lots of people myself and I see this a lot
that happens with people that have streams, especially.
So, you know, my suggestion, not that you asked,
is to remember why you're doing it.
And if it becomes the opposite of why you're doing it,
then remind these people, you know?
And look, I can't read the chat,
although I did catch a couple of comments
because I'm driving, but I have haters everywhere.
I have haters here that doesn't stop me
and that certainly doesn't let it get to me.
I think it means you're doing something right, honestly.
Thank you
Support you I just met you and everything, but I like your channel and I'll be here probably in the mornings and
Thank you. I don't want to be I'm not a panel whore. I'm not going to take up all your panel time
I just wanted to come up and say hello and
Give you my perspective of things. I
appreciate that and thank you so much and I
I appreciate the advice and and I hope to talk to you again soon
Yeah, sure and I love to the kitties and I'll be around you
Okay, love you. Have a great night. Have a good one. You too. Bye-bye.
Okay, okay. Oh, here's Hannah. Here's Hannah. Hello. Oh, no.